Guide to the Wilmarth Sheldon Lewis Papers
The Lewis Walpole Library
- Correspondence, 1901–1979; Series I; 76.56; 181 boxes
  - General Correspondence
    - Holland, David, 1953–1973 (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - Holland Brothers, 1957–1963 (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - Holland Society of New York, 1977 (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - Hollander, David, 1959 (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - Hollings, Frank, 1938–1973 (Box 65, Folder 5)
    - Hollis, C. Carroll (Charles Carroll), 1911-, 1964 (Box 65, Folder 6)
    - Holman, Winifred Lovering, 1899-1989, 1949–1955 (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - Holman's Print Shop, 1971 (Box 65, Folder 8)
    - Holmes, Thomas James, 1874-1959, 1938 (Box 65, Folder 9)
    - Honour, Hugh, 1953–1958 (Box 65, Folder 10)
    - Hook, Lucyle, 1959–1960 (Box 65, Folder 11)
    - Hoose Library of Philosophy, 1970–1973 (Box 65, Folder 12)
    - Hoover, Andrew G., 1909-2001, 1936–1953 (Box 65, Folder 13)
    - Hopkins, Joseph G. E., 1966 (Box 65, Folder 14)
    - Hoppin, William W., Jr., 1949–1979 (Box 65, Folder 15)
    - Horace G. Commin (Firm), 1948–1958 (Box 65, Folder 16)
    - Hordon, John, 1966–1970 (Box 65, Folder 17)
    - Horgan, Paul, 1903-1995, 1966–1978 (Box 65, Folder 18)
    - Hornby, Diana and Rosamund, 1936–1976 (Box 65, Folder 19)
    - Hotson, Leslie, 1897-1992, and Mary, 1952–1964 (Box 65, Folder 20)
    - Houghton, Arthur Amory, 1906-1990, 1938–1957 (Box 65, Folder 21)
    - House & Garden, 1949–1973 (Box 65, Folder 22)
    - House of El Dieff, Inc., 1962–1974 (Box 65, Folder 23)
    - How, George Evelyn Paget, 1952–1953 (Box 65, Folder 24)
    - Howard, George A. C., 1958–1978 (Box 65, Folder 25)
    - Howard W. Lyon, Inc., 1948–1949 (Box 65, Folder 26)
    - Howarth, R. G. (Robert Guy), 1906-1974, 1961 (Box 65, Folder 27)
    - Howarth, David Armine, 1912-1991, 1973–1975 (Box 65, Folder 28)
    - Howd, Helen, 1973–1977 (Box 65, Folder 29)
    - Howe, Harold, II, 1918-2002, 1961–1964 (Box 65, Folder 30)
    - Howe, Mary, 1882-1964, 1949–1963 (Box 65, Folder 31)
    - Howell, J. Taylor and Elizabeth, 1953–1970 (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - Howes, C. (Charles), 1930–1949 (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - Hoye, Wilbur G., 1949–1957 (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - Hoyt, Elton, 1940–1947 (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - Hroswitha Club, 1949–1974 (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - Hudson, Elizabeth, 1946–1972 (Box 66, Folder 6-7)
    - Hudson Shipping Company, 1951–1976 (Box 66, Folder 8)
    - Hughes, Helen Sard, 1882-1955, 1929–1945 (Box 66, Folder 9)
    - Hugo, Harold, 1973–1979 (Box 66, Folder 10)
    - Hulme, George, 1932-, 1974–1975 (Box 66, Folder 11)
    - Hunt, Elizabeth C., 1971–1972 (Box 66, Folder 12)
    - Hunt, Elmer Munson, 1883-1968, 1951–1952 (Box 66, Folder 13)
    - Hunt, John Dixon, 1975–1976 (Box 66, Folder 14)
    - Hunt, Joseph P., 1952–1962 (Box 66, Folder 15)
    - Hunt, Roy Arthur, 1881-1966, 1939–1949 (Box 66, Folder 16)
    - Hunter, Robert E., 1970–1978 (Box 66, Folder 17)
    - Hurlburt, Mabel, 1944–1967 (Box 66, Folder 18)
    - Hutchins, Henry Clinton, 1889-, 1934–1941 (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - Hutchins, Robert Maynard, 1899-1977, 1952–1962 (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - Huxley, Julian, 1887-1975, 1942 (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - Hyatt, Alton R., 1971–1979 (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - Hyde, Donald Frizell, 1909-1966, and Mary, 1946–1979 (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - Ia-Iz, general (Box 67, Folder 6)
    - Ilchester, Giles Stephen Holland Fox-Strangways, Earl of, 1874-1959, 1924–1958 (Box 67, Folder 7)
    - Index Society, 1939–1949 (Box 67, Folder 8)
    - Innis, William S., 1933–1946 (Box 67, Folder 9)
    - Institut et Museé Voltaire, 1937–1961 (Box 67, Folder 10)
    - Iron Worker, 1977 (Box 67, Folder 11)
    - Irving, Robert Grant, 1940-, 1972–1978 (Box 67, Folder 12)
    - Isham, Ralph Heyward, 1890-1955, 1930–1948 (Box 67, Folder 13)
    - Iveagh Bequest, Kenwood (London, England), 1967–1973 (Box 67, Folder 14)
    - Ja-Jz, general (Box 67, Folder 15-16)
    - Jack, Ian, 1935-, 1974–1976 (Box 67, Folder 17)
    - Jackson, Donald, 1919-1987, 1969–1971 (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - Jackson, Sir Henry Cholmondeley, 1946–1972 (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - Jackson, Stuart W. (Stuart Wells), 1875-, 1933–1957 (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - Jackson, William A. (William Alexander), 1905-1964, 1935–1965 (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - Jaffé, Michael, 1923-, 1946–1957 (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - James A. Lewis & Sons, 1949–1950 (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - James F. Drake, Inc., 1945–1960 (Box 68, Folder 7)
    - James Rimell and Son, 1932–1939 (Box 68, Folder 8)
    - James, Macgill, 1935–1972 (Box 68, Folder 9)
    - Janeway, Edward G. and Elinor, 1940-1965 (Box 68, Folder 10)
    - Jansen, George F., 1963–1973 (Box 68, Folder 11)
    - Janson, H. W. (Horst Woldemar), 1913-1982, 1979 (Box 68, Folder 12)
    - Janta, Alexander, 1959–1960 (Box 68, Folder 13)
    - Jeffords, Walter M., 1937–1960 (Box 68, Folder 14)
    - Jemail, Emil E., 1947–1952 (Box 68, Folder 15)
    - Jennings, Annie Burr, 1855-1939, 1928–1939 (Box 68, Folder 16)
    - Jennings, B. Brewster, 1898-, 1939–1963 (Box 68, Folder 17-18)
    - Jennings, Jean, 1934–1937 (Box 68, Folder 19)
    - Jennings, Lawrence K., 1939–1971 (Box 68, Folder 20)
    - Jennings, Oliver Burr, 1928–1969 (Box 68, Folder 21)
    - Jessup, Philip C. (Philip Caryl), 1897-1986, and Lois, 1954–1978 (Box 69, Folder 1-2)
    - Jestin, Heimwarth B., 1948–1979 (Box 69, Folder 3)
    - Jestin, Loftus, 1976–1979 (Box 69, Folder 4)
    - John F. Kennedy Library, 1962–1976 (Box 69, Folder 5-6)
    - John Grant Booksellers, 1937–1952 (Box 69, Folder 7)
    - John McDonough & Sons, 1971–1978 (Box 69, Folder 8)
    - John Hay Fellows, 1955 (Box 69, Folder 9)
    - John Howell Books (San Francisco, Calif.), 1951–1980 (Box 69, Folder 10)
    - John Rothwell (Firm), 1955–1964 (Box 69, Folder 11)
    - Johnson, Philip A., 1960–1971 (Box 69, Folder 12)
    - Johnson, Sherman E. (Sherman Elbridge), 1908-, 1968–1970 (Box 70, Folder 1)
    - Johnson, Ward L., 1952–1977 (Box 70, Folder 2)
    - Johnson House Club, 1934–1963 (Box 70, Folder 3)
    - Johnsonians (Society), 1959–1978 (Box 70, Folder 4)
    - Johnston, Iris, 1950–1974 (Box 70, Folder 5)
    - Johnston, Stephen, 1969–1976 (Box 70, Folder 6)
    - Johnston, Veronica B., 1958–1975 (Box 70, Folder 7)
    - Jones, A. Marshall, 1938–1947 (Box 70, Folder 8)
    - Jones, Chalk and Dawson, 1955–1964 (Box 70, Folder 9)
    - Jones, Claude Edward, 1907, 1938–1959 (Box 70, Folder 10)
    - Jones, Kay, 1976–1979 (Box 70, Folder 11)
    - Jones, Louis C. (Louis Clark), 1908-1990, 1939–1957 (Box 70, Folder 12)
    - Jones, Suzanne P., 1971 (Box 70, Folder 13)
    - Jones, Stephen B., 1950–1973 (Box 70, Folder 14)
    - Jones, William Powell, 1901-, 1933–1976 (Box 70, Folder 15)
    - Joppien, Rüdiger, 1946-, 1971–1972 (Box 70, Folder 16)
    - Jowitt, Leslie, 1962–1963 (Box 70, Folder 17)
    - Joy, James P., 1938–1956 (Box 70, Folder 18)
    - Judd, Gerrit P., 1939–1959 (Box 70, Folder 19)
    - Juel-Jensen, Bent, 1952–1963 (Box 70, Folder 20)
    - Ka-Kz, general (Box 70, Folder 21-22)
    - K. D. Duval (Firm), 1971 (Box 71, Folder 1)
    - Kagen, David H., 1978 (Box 71, Folder 2)
    - Kahn, Edgar M. (Edgar Myron), 1904-1970, 1951–1952 (Box 71, Folder 3)
    - Kaplan, Herbert H., 1959–1962 (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - Kates, George N. (George Norbert), 1895-1990, 1951–1976 (Box 71, Folder 5)
    - Kaufman, Paul, 1967–1970 (Box 71, Folder 6)
    - Keator, Samuel J., 1939–1940 (Box 71, Folder 7)
    - Keefe, Kate, 1966 (Box 71, Folder 8)
    - Keep, Robert P. and Rose A. D., 1959–1967 (Box 71, Folder 9)
    - Keller, Deane, 1901-1992, 1948–1964 (Box 71, Folder 10)
    - Keller, Kate Van Winkle, 1979 (Box 71, Folder 11)
    - Kenefick, Theodore G., 1945–1972 (Box 71, Folder 12)
    - Kennedy, John F. (John Fitzgerald), 1917-1963, 1954 (Box 71, Folder 13)
    - Kennedy, Máire, 1951–1965 (Box 71, Folder 14)
    - Kennedy, Robert F., 1925-1968, 1964–1968 (Box 71, Folder 15)
    - Kennedy, Walter, 1971–1977 (Box 71, Folder 16)
    - Kennerley, Eija, 1977–1978 (Box 71, Folder 17)
    - Kenneth W. Rendell, Inc., 1974–1976 (Box 71, Folder 18)
    - Kent, Sherman, 1938–1974 (Box 71, Folder 19)
    - Kent, William, Jr., 1946–1962 (Box 71, Folder 20)
    - Kenyon, L. F. R., 1957–1959 (Box 71, Folder 21)
    - Kenyon, Lloyd Tyrell-Kenyon, Baron, 1917-1993, 1960–1971 (Box 71, Folder 22)
    - Keogh, Andrew, 1869-1953, 1931–1951 (Box 71, Folder 23)
    - Kerr, Chester Brooks, 1913-1999, 1941–1979 (Box 71, Folder 24-25)
    - Kerr, John, 1927-2018, 1960–1961 (Box 72, Folder 1)
    - Kerslake, John F., 1967–1969 (Box 72, Folder 2)
    - Ketton-Cremer, R. W. (Robert Wyndham), 1906-1969, 1931–1961 (Box 72, Folder 3-6)
    - Ketton-Cremer, R. W. (Robert Wyndham), 1906-1969, 1962–1970 (Box 73, Folder 1)
    - Keynes, Geoffrey, 1887-1982, and Quentin, 1940–1977 (Box 73, Folder 2)
    - Keynes, Milo, 1968 (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - Kilbourn, Orrin P., 1956 (Box 73, Folder 4)
    - Kilby, Clyde S., 1937–1949 (Box 73, Folder 5)
    - Kiley, Mark, 1940–1950 (Box 73, Folder 6)
    - Kilgour, Frederick G., 1946–1964 (Box 73, Folder 7)
    - Kimball, Richard A. and Josephine D., 1935–1978 (Box 73, Folder 8-9)
    - Kindler, Hans, 1892-1949, 1947–1949 (Box 74, Folder 1)
    - King, Frederic R. and Epsie, 1960–1967 (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - King, Harold and Shirley, 1952–1973 (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - Kingman, Gilbert, 1959–1964 (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - King's College (University of Cambridge), 1937–1955 (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - King's College (University of Cambridge). Library, 1977 (Box 74, Folder 6)
    - King's Lynn (England), 1959 (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - Kingsford, R. J. L. (Reginald John Lethbridge), 1900-1978, 1966–1967 (Box 74, Folder 8)
    - Kinney, Arthur F., 1933-, 1962–1965 (Box 74, Folder 9)
    - Kinsella, Frank D., 1963 (Box 74, Folder 10)
    - Kirby, J. P. (John Pendy), 1927–1961 (Box 74, Folder 11)
    - Kirsop, Wallace, 1972–1978 (Box 74, Folder 12)
    - Klebs, Arnold C. (Arnold Carl), 1870-1943, 1939–1940 (Box 74, Folder 13)
    - Klein, Arthur Luce, 1962 (Box 74, Folder 14)
    - Knapp, Clarence H., 1949 (Box 74, Folder 15)
    - Knapp, Lewis M. (Lewis Mansfield), 1963 (Box 74, Folder 16)
    - Kneeland, Yale, 1901-, 1943–1966 (Box 74, Folder 17)
    - Knight, Ridgway B., 1968 (Box 74, Folder 18)
    - Knollenberg, Bernhard, 1892-1973, 1938–1959 (Box 74, Folder 19-20)
    - Knollenberg, Bernhard, 1892-1973, 1960–1972 (Box 75, Folder 1-2)
    - Knopf, Alfred A., 1892-1984, 1952–1979 (Box 75, Folder 3-4)
      The folders hold correspondence with Knopf, as well as with his wives Blanche Wolf Knopf (1894-1966) and Helen Hedrick Knopf (1902-1995), and with staff members at the publishing house Alfred A. Knopf. Correspondence and other material related to books by Lewis published by Knopf is filed in Series III. Writings.
    - Knox, John B., 1946–1969 (Box 75, Folder 5)
    - Knox, Seymour H., 1898-1990, 1945–1967 (Box 75, Folder 6)
    - Koch, Ruth, 1937–1960 (Box 75, Folder 7)
    - Koch, Theodore Wesley, 1871-1941, 1934–1935 (Box 75, Folder 8)
    - Koninklijke Bibliotheek (Netherlands), 1949–1968 (Box 75, Folder 9)
    - Korshin, Paul J., 1939-2005, 1968–1975 (Box 76, Folder 1)
    - Krumbhaar, E. B. (Edward Bell), 1882-1966, 1965 (Box 76, Folder 2)
    - Kuch, John S., 1953 (Box 76, Folder 3)
    - La-Lz, general (Box 76, Folder 4-6)
    - Labouisse, Sally, 1956–1979 (Box 76, Folder 7)
    - Ladd, Frederick J., 1978–1979 (Box 76, Folder 8)
    - LaFarge, Henry A., 1957–1959 (Box 76, Folder 9)
    - Lakeside Press (Chicago, Ill.), 1938–1973 (Box 76, Folder 10)
    - Lam, George Lorant
      - Correspondence, 1937–1955 (Box 77, Folder 1-5)
      - Correspondence, 1956–1970 (Box 78, Folder 1-4)
      - Correspondence with Warren H. Smith, 1952–1954 (Box 78, Folder 5)
      - Correspondence with Warren H. Smith, 1955–1964 (Box 79, Folder 1)
      - Lists and notes, 1952–1962 (Box 79, Folder 2-3)
    - Lamb, James G., 1958–1959 (Box 79, Folder 4)
    - Lambert, Elizabeth, 1979 (Box 79, Folder 5)
    - Lamont, Thomas S. and Ellie, 1953–1972 (Box 79, Folder 6)
    - Lamson, Roy, 1908-1986, 1939–1948 (Box 79, Folder 7)
    - Lane, Mills B. (Mills Bee), 1912-1989, 1970–1978 (Box 79, Folder 8)
    - Langan, John Francis, 1944–1978 (Box 80, Folder 1-2)
    - Langan, John Francis, Jr., 1979 (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - Langedijk, Karla, 1977 (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - Langer, William L. (William Leonard), 1896-1977, 1945–1975 (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - Langham, Pat, 1966 (Box 80, Folder 6)
    - Lansdowne, Lord, 1933–1952 (Box 80, Folder 7)
    - Larner, Lucy, 1939 (Box 80, Folder 8)
    - Laski, Harold Joseph, 1893-1950, 1947–1953 (Box 80, Folder 9)
    - Lathrop C. Harper, Inc., 1944–1966 (Box 80, Folder 10)
    - Lavender, David, 1910-2003, 1961–1967 (Box 80, Folder 11)
    - Law Society's Hall, 1951–1959 (Box 80, Folder 12)
    - Lawrence, George S., 1940–1972 (Box 80, Folder 13)
    - Lawrence, John T. and Helen, 1939–1970 (Box 80, Folder 14)
    - Lawrence, Richard H., 1939–1975 (Box 80, Folder 15)
    - Lawrence, Virginia, 1966 (Box 80, Folder 16)
    - Lazor, Michael Z., 1979 (Box 80, Folder 17)
    - Leekley, Richard, 1971 (Box 80, Folder 18)
    - Leffingwell, R. C. (Russell Cornell), 1878-1960, 1934–1957 (Box 80, Folder 19)
    - Leggatt Brothers, 1935–1957 (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - Leicester, Thomas William Coke, Earl of, 1848-1941, 1935–1936 (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - Leisenring, Julie, 1972–1979 (Box 81, Folder 3)
    - Leishman, Marista, 1975–1976 (Box 81, Folder 4)
    - LeMaitre, Evelyn, 1955 (Box 81, Folder 5)
    - Lennard, Suzanne H. Crowhurst, 1976 (Box 81, Folder 6)
    - Leona Rostenberg (Firm), 1951–1977 (Box 81, Folder 7)
    - Leone, Sister Mary Anne, 1938 (Box 81, Folder 8)
    - Leonard, Joseph, 1877-1964, 1932–1964 (Box 81, Folder 9-12)
    - Leslie, Shane, 1885-1971, 1937–1958 (Box 81, Folder 13)
    - Leslie-Melville, A. R., 1935 (Box 81, Folder 14)
    - Lever, Tresham, 1900-1975, 1949–1962 (Box 81, Folder 15)
    - Levinson, Harry A., 1944–1959 (Box 82, Folder 1)
    - Lévy, Maurice, 1959–1971 (Box 82, Folder 2)
    - Lewis, Alison S., 1969–1976 (Box 82, Folder 3)
    - Lewis, Harland S., 1958–1972 (Box 82, Folder 4)
    - Lewis, Lesley, 1961–1963 (Box 82, Folder 5)
    - Lewis, R. W. B. (Richard Warrington Baldwin), 1968 (Box 82, Folder 6)
    - Lewis, Sinclair, 1885-1951, 1937–1941 (Box 82, Folder 7)
    - Library of Congress, 1936–1979 (Box 82, Folder 8)
    - Liebert, Herman ("Fritz") W., 1939–1979 (Box 82, Folder 9-10)
    - Liebmann, Alfred J., 1954–1955 (Box 82, Folder 11)
    - Life Magazine, 1944–1969 (Box 82, Folder 12)
    - Lincoln, Evelyn, 1909-1995, 1964–1965 (Box 82, Folder 13)
    - Lindsay, Daryl and Joanne, 1945–1976 (Box 82, Folder 14-15)
    - Lindsay, George N., 1979 (Box 83, Folder 1)
    - Linfield, H. S., 1954–1964 (Box 83, Folder 2)
    - Lionel & Philip Robinson, Ltd., 1957–1965 (Box 83, Folder 3)
    - Lippmann, Walter, 1889-1974, 1940–1974 (Box 83, Folder 4)
    - Little, Bertram K., 1899-1993, 1954–1976 (Box 83, Folder 5)
    - Little, David M., 1936 (Box 83, Folder 6)
    - Little, Katherine Day, 1950 (Box 83, Folder 7)
    - Livermore, George, 1974–1979 (Box 83, Folder 8)
    - Liverpool (England). Public Libraries, Museums, and Art Gallery, 1937–1951 (Box 83, Folder 9)
    - Livingston, Dorothy F., 1949–1965 (Box 83, Folder 10)
    - Lloyd-Jacob, Clare, 1975 (Box 83, Folder 11)
    - Lloyd-Johnes, Herbert, 1960 (Box 83, Folder 12)
    - Lloyd-Jones, Daphne C., 1952–1953 (Box 83, Folder 13)
    - Lloyd-Smith, Marjorie, 1944–1949 (Box 83, Folder 14)
    - Lobb, John, 1940–1970 (Box 83, Folder 15)
    - Lohmann, Carl A. (Carl Albert), 1887-, 1931–1957 (Box 83, Folder 16)
    - Lombard, Lawrence M., 1965 (Box 83, Folder 17)
    - Londonberry, Edith, 1951 (Box 83, Folder 18)
    - Longmore, Darrell E., 1962–1972 (Box 83, Folder 19)
    - Lonsdale, James Hugh William Lowther, Earl of, 1959–1960 (Box 83, Folder 20)
    - Loomis, F. Kent, 1964–1967 (Box 83, Folder 21)
    - Loomis, James Lee, 1946–1962 (Box 83, Folder 22)
    - Lord, George de Forest, 1919-, 1956–1968 (Box 83, Folder 23)
    - Lord, William G., 1947–1971 (Box 83, Folder 24)
    - Loring, Augustus Peabody, 1856-1938, 1940–1979 (Box 83, Folder 25)
    - Lothian, Peter Francis Walter Kerr, Marquess of, 1957–1976 (Box 83, Folder 26)
    - Lovett, Sidney, 1958–1966 (Box 83, Folder 27)
    - Lowe Bros. Ltd., 1940–1961 (Box 83, Folder 28)
    - Lowenhaupt, Warren Hiram, 1891-1967, 1954–1965 (Box 84, Folder 1)
    - Lugt, Frits, 1884-1970, 1941–1953 (Box 84, Folder 2)
    - Lunt, Alfred, 1977 (Box 84, Folder 3)
    - Luttrell, Alys, 1956–1968 (Box 84, Folder 4)
    - Lydenberg, Harry Miller, 1874-1960, 1935–1952 (Box 84, Folder 5)
    - Lyttelton, Anthony, 1958 (Box 84, Folder 6)
    - Ma-Mz, general (Box 84, Folder 7-11)
    - Mabbott, Thomas Ollive, 1898-1968, 1935–1951 (Box 85, Folder 1)
    - Macalister, Margaret, 1938–1954 (Box 85, Folder 2)
    - Macksey, Richard, 1931-, 1974 (Box 85, Folder 3)
    - McAdam, E. L. (Edward Lippincott), 1905-1969, 1940–1968 (Box 85, Folder 4)
    - McAlpin, David H. (David Hunter), 1897-1989, 1947–1975 (Box 85, Folder 5)
    - McCabe, Charles, 1915-, 1973–1975 (Box 85, Folder 6)
    - McCabe, Kevin, 1972–1975 (Box 85, Folder 7)
    - McCarron, Paul, 1979 (Box 85, Folder 8)
    - McCarthy, Elizabeth, 1963 (Box 85, Folder 9)
    - McCarthy, Francis I., 1962–1963 (Box 85, Folder 10)
    - McCarthy, Julia T., 1941–1964 (Box 85, Folder 11-12)
    - McCarthy, Lily, 1954 (Box 85, Folder 13)
    - McCarthy, Michael J., 1939-, 1969–1978 (Box 85, Folder 14-16)
    - McCarthy, William H., Jr., 1938–1956 (Box 86, Folder 1)
    - McCaskey, William Spencer, 1969 (Box 86, Folder 2)
    - McClintock, Gilbert S., 1938 (Box 86, Folder 3)
    - McClure, Robert E., 1974 (Box 86, Folder 4)
    - McClure, Ruth K., 1916-, 1975–1979 (Box 86, Folder 5)
    - McClure-Smith, H. A. (Hugh Alexander) and Polly, 1945–1978 (Box 86, Folder 6)
    - McConnell, John W., 1946–1977 (Box 86, Folder 7)
    - McCord, David Thompson Watson, 1897-1997, 1940–1957 (Box 86, Folder 8)
    - McCorkle, Elizabeth O., 1936 (Box 86, Folder 9)
    - McCrillis, John O. C, 1973–1975 (Box 86, Folder 10)
    - Maccubbin, Robert P., 1972 (Box 86, Folder 11)
    - MacCunn, Florence A. (Florence Anne), 1857-1939, 1924 (Box 86, Folder 12)
    - MacDermot, P. R., 1961 (Box 86, Folder 13)
    - Macdonald, Ronald, 1947–1950 (Box 86, Folder 14)
    - McDonnell, John, 1955–1963 (Box 86, Folder 15)
    - McFarlane, K. B. (Kenneth Bruce), 1936–1948 (Box 86, Folder 16)
    - Mack, Maynard, 1909-2001, 1938–1977 (Box 86, Folder 17)
    - McKelligott, Nancy, 1971 (Box 86, Folder 18)
    - McKelvey, Susan Delano, 1936–1964 (Box 86, Folder 19)
      Biographical / Historical
      Susan Delano McKelvey (1883-1964), a botanist, was the sister of the Lewises' close friends William Adams Delano and Moreau Delano. Her folder includes a letter to her from Annie Lewis, thanking McKelvey for sending a nineteenth-century carved wooden eagle to the Lewises, with an attached photo showing the eagle mounted on an exterior wall of the Cowles House. The Lewises had long admired the eagle, a ship stern board, when they visited the New Jersey home of Moreau Delano, and it was a gift to them upon his death.
    - McKenzie, Alan T., 1973–1974 (Box 86, Folder 20)
    - McKeon, Edith, 1965–1966 (Box 86, Folder 21)
    - McKibbon, David, 1948–1967 (Box 86, Folder 22)
    - Mackworth-Young, Robin, 1969–1978 (Box 86, Folder 23)
    - McLaughlin, Charles Capen, 1964–1972 (Box 86, Folder 24)
    - McLean, Mary T., 1952–1978 (Box 86, Folder 25)
    - MacLeish, Archibald, 1892-1982, and Ada, 1936–1979 (Box 87, Folder 1-3)
    - McLeish & Sons, 1946–1956 (Box 87, Folder 4)
    - McLennon, Donald, 1952 (Box 87, Folder 5)
    - McMullen, Walter J. and Helen, 1969 (Box 87, Folder 6)
    - McNalty, Bruce, 1938–1939 (Box 87, Folder 7)
    - McNiel, Robert O., 1945–1967 (Box 87, Folder 8)
    - MacVicar, Mary, 1972 (Box 87, Folder 9)
    - Madan, Geoffrey, 1895-1947, 1932 (Box 87, Folder 10)
    - Madden, Henry, 1952–1955 (Box 87, Folder 11)
    - Madden, James Stanley, 1976–1978 (Box 87, Folder 12)
    - Madison, Marshall P., 1949–1977 (Box 87, Folder 13)
    - Magnus-Allcroft, Philip, 1948–1965 (Box 87, Folder 14)
    - Magee, James M. (James McDevitt), 1877-1949, 1940 (Box 87, Folder 15)
    - Maggs Bros., 1925–1939 (Box 87, Folder 16)
    - Maggs Bros., 1940–1959 (Box 88, Folder 1-5)
    - Maggs Bros., 1959–1979 (Box 89, Folder 1-2)
    - Mahoney, Michael, 1975 (Box 89, Folder 3)
    - Mainwaring, Richard, 1965–1974 (Box 89, Folder 4)
    - Makepeace, Roy, 1938–1976 (Box 89, Folder 5)
    - Mallett and Son Antiques, 1934–1956 (Box 89, Folder 6)
    - Malloch, Archibald, 1887-, 1936 (Box 89, Folder 7)
    - Malone, Dumas, 1892-1986, 1972 (Box 89, Folder 8)
    - Mancall, Rosamund, 1973–1977 (Box 89, Folder 9)
    - Mann, Colin and Iris, 1965–1978 (Box 89, Folder 10)
    - Mann, Elizabeth L., 1960 (Box 89, Folder 11)
    - Mann, Thomas, 1875-1955, and Klaus, 1938–1941 (Box 89, Folder 12)
    - Mannheim, M. J., 1957–1970 (Box 89, Folder 13)
    - Manuscript Society (U.S.), 1951–1954 (Box 89, Folder 14)
    - Manwaring, Elizabeth Wheeler, 1879-, 1938–1947 (Box 89, Folder 15)
    - Maracarco, Anthony, 1972–1977 (Box 89, Folder 16)
    - Markham, Sarah, 1975–1979 (Box 89, Folder 17)
    - Marsh, Dorothy, 1965–1976 (Box 89, Folder 18)
    - Martin, Alastair Bradley, 1953–1968 (Box 89, Folder 19)
    - Martin Breslauer, Inc., 1944–1959 (Box 90, Folder 1)
    - Martin, George Whitney, 1887-1959, 1950–1959 (Box 90, Folder 2)
    - Martin, Mabel, 1949–1973 (Box 90, Folder 3)
    - Martin, Mary, 1975–1978 (Box 90, Folder 4)
    - Martin, William McChesney, 1962–1978 (Box 90, Folder 5)
    - Martz, Edwine M., 1942–1979 (Box 90, Folder 6)
    - Martz, Louis L. (Louis Lohr), 1913-2001, 1949–1979 (Box 90, Folder 7)
    - Masefield, John, 1878-1967, 1919–1931 (Box 90, Folder 8)
    - Mason, William S., 1940–1952 (Box 90, Folder 9)
    - Massachusetts Historical Society, 1935–1979 (Box 90, Folder 10)
    - Massey, Gerald, 1937–1943 (Box 90, Folder 11)
    - Mathews, Alister, 1950–1963 (Box 90, Folder 12)
    - Mathews, T. S., 1977 (Box 90, Folder 13)
    - Mauran, Frank, 1937–1940 (Box 90, Folder 14)
    - Maxfield, Ezra Kempton, 1938–1939 (Box 90, Folder 15)
    - Maxim, Hiram Hamilton, 1976–1977 (Box 90, Folder 16)
    - May, Georges, 1920-, 1964–1974 (Box 90, Folder 17)
    - Mayer, John, 1968–1979 (Box 90, Folder 18)
    - Mayor, A. Hyatt (Alpheus Hyatt), 1901-1980, 1964–1975 (Box 90, Folder 19)
    - MD Medical Newsmagazine, 1976–1979 (Box 90, Folder 20)
    - Medcalf, James E., 1946–1947 (Box 90, Folder 21)
    - Medley, John Dudley Gibbs, 1891-1962, 1946–1952 (Box 90, Folder 22)
    - Meek, Samuel W. (Samuel Williams), 1895-, 1949–1973 (Box 90, Folder 23)
    - Meeks, Carroll L. V. (Carroll Louis Vanderslice), 1907-1966, 1961–1962 (Box 90, Folder 24)
    - Meeks, Everett V. (Everett Victor), 1879-1954, 1934–1949 (Box 90, Folder 25)
    - Mein, Sally, 1974–1979 (Box 91, Folder 1)
    - Mellon, Paul, 1940–1969 (Box 91, Folder 2)
    - Mendell, Clarence W. (Clarence Whittlesey), 1883-1970, 1940–1971 (Box 91, Folder 3)
    - Mendenhall, Thomas C. (Thomas Corwin), 1910-1998, 1957 (Box 91, Folder 4)
    - Mercantile Library, 1933–1973 (Box 91, Folder 5)
    - Merck, George W., 1977–1978 (Box 91, Folder 6)
    - Meriden Gravure Company, 1960–1979 (Box 91, Folder 7)
    - Merriman, Robert, 1967–1968 (Box 91, Folder 8)
    - Merritt, Percival, 1860-1932, and Elisabeth, 1927–1940 (Box 91, Folder 9)
    - Mersey, Charles Clive Bigham, Viscount, 1872-1956, 1934–1938 (Box 91, Folder 10)
    - Metcalfe, John, 1947–1953 (Box 91, Folder 11)
    - Metcalf, Keyes DeWitt, 1889-1983, 1938–1978 (Box 91, Folder 12)
    - Metropolitan Club (Washington, D.C.), 1949–1979 (Box 91, Folder 13)